It's so cute.
Which one do you like?
Hello.
I'm Mina Koike from Murazaka46.
Today is my day off.
I'd like to go on a date with my dog, Pon.
Hey, Pon-chan!
Please show us your picture.
This is Pon.
This is my dog, Pon.
It's hard to get him to look at me.
He won't look at me at all.
Today, I'd like to go out with Pon.
I'd like to go out with Pon today.
And then...
There's a place I've always wanted to go.
I want to go there with Pon.
I want to make Pon happy today
I want to make today a day to make Pon happy.
Pon-chan!
Pon-chan, over here!
Hey, Po-chan!
O-chan, you went this way today.
I came to Yokohama once with Kabu in April.
This is the second time I've been to Yokohama for something other than work.
This is the second time I've come to Yokohama as a private visitor
Surprisingly, I've never been here before.
I've never been here before.
I haven't been outside much lately.
It's hot, isn't it, Banana?
It's so hot!
The reason I originally wanted to buy a com...
I've wanted to get a dog ever since I moved to Tokyo.
I had been in Tokyo for about four years, and I still felt the same way.
I was confident that I could definitely raise a dog.
Right in front of me now...
Ta-da!
Sea
And then, poof!
The ocean.
It's the ocean.
Isn't it amazing? Isn't it too beautiful?
Well, it's not the first time I've seen the ocean since I came to Tokyo.
Not the first time.
But it's not the first time.
Oh, you stopped, Poco.
Are you tired? You want me to hold you?
He wants me to hold him, so I'll hold him.
Clouds... they're about to become summer clouds.
It's a good time of year, isn't it, Poco?
I'm ready.
Clouds don't like to be held.
It's not a place at the bottom of the sea.
I'm down!
I'd like to go to Nishisuke
Hey, girl!
Hello
The hand cutter is doing it
Thank you
You're a ruffian.
Today's combo is a rambunctious one.
I've got him.
This is a very nice room.
I wonder what he'll eat.
I'm looking forward to it.
So cute!
Sit, sit, sit.
Sit.
Sit down?
Sit?
Sit.
He won't do it.
Well, I'll order you something.
Oh, my God.
Let's see what you want.
You don't like fruit, do you?
Do you want to try one?
You won't eat it.
Do you want the one with strawberries in it?
Like this one here? Which one do you like?
Hey, hey, hey.
Pop-pop.
So cute!
One Loose S and Strawberry Sweet Potato, please.
Yes, please.
In terms of today's menu, there's a lot of com's favorite foods, right?
I especially like white meat, sweet potatoes and broccoli, but I don't like strawberries.
But he doesn't like strawberries, and he won't eat them if I give them to him as they are.
Today's recipe is strawberry sweet potato, so I thought it might be a good chance to make him like strawberries.
So, thank you very much for watching!
Pom, are you crying?
I'm crying a little.
Maybe he likes the waiter.
Pom is a boy.
He loves human women.I love human women.
More so than doggy girls.
He loves human women more than doggy girls.
Doooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
Wow, that was cute.
Now that was cute.
Here you go.
Here's your strawberry tweet.
Thank you very much.
Here's today's Shumi.
Please enjoy it as it is.
Yes, thank you.
Like this.
This is Strawberry's tweet.
This is a strawberry tweet.
Thank you very much.
It looks like this.
Pom is very interested in this.
This is, uh, what was it?
This way
One-loop loin.
One loin with something next to it.
Carrot sauce next to it? It's got some kind of carrot sauce next to it.
Pom, no.
This is strawberry sweet potato.
I want you to try these, Pom.
Just a minute. I'm gonna bake it now.
I'm going to go.
I'll just have one at a time.
Just one.
Oh, I'm looking forward to it.
I'll cook the meat.
I'm going to grill the meat.
Sit down.
Good job! Yes!
Mmm-hmm.
You didn't do it before.
Mmm.
It's been a while today.
How's your outing?
Mm-hmm.
You've been happy.
Do you want to try some sweet potatoes?
I'll have some.
Eat
Eat.
Yeah!
Yay!
Did I get it?
Yeah!
I got it.
For you, Bomu.
This is
Strawberry Sweet Potato
I'd like to fry them
I'd like to deep fry them 🐬.
Pyohejoki goats
Yummy? Delicious? They ate it.
He ate it.
Oh, they're baked.
Carrot sauce.
Do you think there's enough?
Maybe a little more.
Can we eat it?
Oh, is it good?
Let's try a little carrot sauce.
Oh, that's hard.
It's wild when you eat it.
Hey, how do you like the carrot sauce?
Is it good?
Taste good?
Yummy?
Tasty?
Is everything okay?
It's just me and Pom.
I hope you don't mind that it's just me and Pom on holiday.
I hope my solo sound is amazing.
You like it, don't you?
I hope it's a good start for you to eat strawberries.
I go to cafes with Pom.
But when we go to the café, it's not just me and Pom.
I have a best friend from junior high school.
She's in Tokyo.
I go to cafes and dog parks with her dog.
I go to cafes and dog runs with her dog.
But when we go to the dog run, he doesn't really run.
When I run, he just follows behind me on foot.
While other dogs are running like crazy.
My friend's dog was also running, but Pom just wouldn't run.
I'm always looking at him.
But he likes to play and have fun.
So when we go to a dog run or something like that, he doesn't play with us.
Jagai, oh!
Wow!
So you've finally become that kind of girl.
Now that he's tasted meat, he won't eat potatoes anymore.Now that I know what meat tastes like, I don't eat potatoes anymore.
What do you think?
Wow.
You're really like that.
There are other members who have dogs besides me.
Fuyuka Saito and Emulyarena also have dogs.
Fu-chan's dog and Pom are not so different in age.
They have been supporting each other since they were puppies.
They have been supporting each other since they were both puppies, and they would say, "We have too many dogs.
They gave us treats and drinks, such as Pocari for dogs.
Rena is also a dog of the same breed as me.
I got some doggy cookies for Valentine's Day.
It was the first Valentine's Day Pom received.
I was like, "That's mine, don't touch it.
I'm grateful that we can share so many things.
I personally think that one of our members, Yui Takemoto, has a face just like Pom's.
I was talking about it with her before.
I'd like to have her face to face with Pom.
There's only a little time left, Pom.
That's it.
Thank you for the food, Mi-chan!
Good job!
Good job, sitting up!
It was delicious!
I ate some meat that I don't usually eat.
And some fruits that I don't like so much.
So today was a great day for us.
It was a great day!
Pom was so happy to eat.
Pom was so happy to eat, so I thought this video
I hope you enjoy the video.
Please let me know how you and your dog are doing.
Please let me know how you and your dogs are doing in the comments section.
Thank you for watching today!
Please like and subscribe to our channel!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
See you soon!
Good night.